[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is the name of the Griffin family's pet dog?",
    "options": [
      "Brian",
      "Stewie",
      "Peter",
      "Chris"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Brian"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is the name of Peter Griffin's wife?",
    "options": [
      "Lois",
      "Meg",
      "Bonnie",
      "Diane"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Lois"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What is the name of the Griffins' eldest son?",
    "options": [
      "Chris",
      "Stewie",
      "Brian",
      "Peter"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Chris"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What is the name of the baby in the Griffin family who is highly intelligent and has a British accent?",
    "options": [
      "Chris",
      "Meg",
      "Stewie",
      "Brian"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Stewie"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What is the name of Peter Griffin's best friend who is a paraplegic and uses a wheelchair?",
    "options": [
      "Quagmire",
      "Cleveland",
      "Mort",
      "Joe"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Joe"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is the name of the local pub where Peter and his friends often hang out?",
    "options": [
      "The Drunken Clam",
      "The Tipsy Tavern",
      "The Boozy Bar",
      "The Sloshed Saloon"
    ],
    "correct_option": "The Drunken Clam"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Who is the Greased-Up Deaf Guy?",
    "options": [
      "Peter Griffin's neighbor",
      "A recurring character on the show",
      "The Griffins' mailman",
      "The town mayor"
    ],
    "correct_option": "A recurring character on the show"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What is the name of Peter Griffin's favorite TV show that features a giant chicken as his nemesis?",
    "options": [
      "The Cluckinator",
      "Fowl Play",
      "Giant Chicken Showdown",
      "The Chicken Fight"
    ],
    "correct_option": "The Chicken Fight"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What is the name of the talking, alcoholic dog in the show?",
    "options": [
      "Brian",
      "Stewie",
      "Chris",
      "Peter"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Brian"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Who is the youngest member of the Griffin family and often engages in diabolical schemes?",
    "options": [
      "Stewie",
      "Meg",
      "Lois",
      "Brian"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Stewie"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Which Griffin family member works at the Quahog Piano Company?",
    "options": [
      "Peter",
      "Lois",
      "Chris",
      "Meg"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Lois"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "Identify the Griffin family's neighbor, known for his social awkwardness and employment at the Happy-Go-Lucky Toy Factory.",
    "options": [
      "Cleveland",
      "Joe",
      "Quagmire",
      "Herbert"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Cleveland"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What is the name of Stewie's teddy bear, often involved in his schemes?",
    "options": [
      "Rupert",
      "Snuggles",
      "Teddy",
      "Cuddles"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Rupert"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "In Family Guy, which character is known for his distinct laugh and works at the Drunken Clam?",
    "options": [
      "Quagmire",
      "Cleveland",
      "Joe",
      "Herbert"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Quagmire"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Who is the patriarch of the Griffin family and often employed at the Pawtucket Brewery?",
    "options": [
      "Peter",
      "Stewie",
      "Chris",
      "Meg"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Peter"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "In Family Guy, who is often seen with a football-shaped head and known for his intelligence?",
    "options": [
      "Stewie",
      "Meg",
      "Lois",
      "Brian"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Stewie"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "Who is the mayor of Quahog in Family Guy?",
    "options": [
      "Mayor West",
      "Mayor Quimby",
      "Mayor McCheese",
      "Mayor Adam West"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Mayor West"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "Which character is known for his obsession with all things pop culture, including his catchphrase 'Giggity'?",
    "options": [
      "Peter",
      "Stewie",
      "Quagmire",
      "Joe"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Quagmire"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What is the name of Stewie's half-brother, who is the child of Peter and his ex-girlfriend?",
    "options": [
      "Bertram",
      "Mort",
      "Neil",
      "Kevin"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Bertram"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "Which character runs a pharmacy in Quahog and often interacts with the Griffin family?",
    "options": [
      "Mort",
      "Dr. Hartman",
      "Herbert",
      "Cleveland"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Mort"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "In Family Guy, who is the news anchor and often appears in cutaway gags?",
    "options": [
      "Tom Tucker",
      "Diane Simmons",
      "Tricia Takanawa",
      "Ollie Williams"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Tom Tucker"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What is the name of Stewie's time-traveling future self who tries to prevent his own demise?",
    "options": [
      "Stu",
      "Bertram",
      "Vinny",
      "Bitch Stewie"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Bitch Stewie"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "Who is the owner of the Drunken Clam, the local bar frequented by Peter and his friends?",
    "options": [
      "Jerome",
      "Cleveland",
      "Horace",
      "Mort"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Horace"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "Which character is Peter's boss at the Pawtucket Brewery?",
    "options": [
      "Angela",
      "Mr. Weed",
      "Opie",
      "Seamus"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Angela"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What is the name of Stewie's nemesis, the child of Peter's co-worker?",
    "options": [
      "Neil",
      "Kevin",
      "Jake",
      "Bertram"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Kevin"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "In Family Guy, who is the elderly neighbor known for his questionable interactions with Chris?",
    "options": [
      "Cleveland",
      "Herbert",
      "Quagmire",
      "Mort"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Herbert"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What is the name of Lois's wealthy and eccentric father?",
    "options": [
      "Carter Pewterschmidt",
      "Mort Goldman",
      "Tom Tucker",
      "Mayor West"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Carter Pewterschmidt"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "Which character is Peter's handicapped friend who occasionally uses a wheelchair?",
    "options": [
      "Joe",
      "Quagmire",
      "Cleveland",
      "Herbert"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Joe"
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What is the name of the local convenience store frequently visited by the Griffin family?",
    "options": [
      "Quik-E-Mart",
      "Stewie's Stop",
      "Kwik-E-Mart",
      "Stewie's Mart"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Quik-E-Mart"
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "Identify the Griffin family's eccentric neighbor who often provides bizarre advice.",
    "options": [
      "Cleveland",
      "Joe",
      "Quagmire",
      "Herbert"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Herbert"
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What is the name of the Griffin family's evil, anthropomorphic monkey who lives in Chris's closet?",
    "options": [
      "Mr. Bananas",
      "Evil Monkey",
      "Spanky",
      "Curious George"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Evil Monkey"
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "In Family Guy, which character is Peter's biological father?",
    "options": [
      "Francis",
      "Mickey McFinnigan",
      "Thelma Griffin",
      "Carter Pewterschmidt"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Francis"
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "Who is the Griffin family member known for her unpopular and frequently mocked opinions?",
    "options": [
      "Lois",
      "Meg",
      "Stewie",
      "Tricia Takanawa"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Meg"
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "Identify the anthropomorphic dog who is Peter's best friend and often seen with a martini.",
    "options": [
      "Spike",
      "Rover",
      "Brian",
      "Max"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Brian"
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "question": "What is the name of the elderly man who is a regular at the Drunken Clam and often yells 'You bastards!'?",
    "options": [
      "Mickey McFinnigan",
      "Herbert",
      "Angry Old Man",
      "Opie"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Angry Old Man"
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "question": "In Family Guy, which character is known for his various jobs and bizarre accidents, such as the exploding cat launcher?",
    "options": [
      "Mort",
      "Cleveland",
      "Quagmire",
      "Joe"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Quagmire"
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "question": "What is the name of Peter Griffin's favorite bar in Quahog?",
    "options": [
      "The Drunken Clam",
      "The Tipsy Turtle",
      "The Giggity Goblet",
      "The Quahog Quencher"
    ],
    "correct_option": "The Drunken Clam"
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "question": "Which character is known for his obsession with birds and owns a parrot named Polynesia?",
    "options": [
      "Peter",
      "Joe",
      "Quagmire",
      "Cleveland"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Joe"
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "question": "In Family Guy, who is the Griffins' eccentric neighbor that has a crush on Chris?",
    "options": [
      "Cleveland",
      "Herbert",
      "Quagmire",
      "Mort"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Herbert"
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "What is the name of the Griffin family's anthropomorphic pet who is a sophisticated and well-spoken dog?",
    "options": [
      "Rover",
      "Brian",
      "Spot",
      "Max"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Brian"
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "question": "Who is Peter Griffin's boss at the Happy-Go-Lucky Toy Factory?",
    "options": [
      "Mr. Weed",
      "Angela",
      "Opie",
      "Seamus"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Mr. Weed"
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "question": "Identify the Griffin family member who frequently gets bullied at school and faces various teenage struggles.",
    "options": [
      "Chris",
      "Meg",
      "Stewie",
      "Brian"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Meg"
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "question": "In Family Guy, which character is the mayor of Quahog and is known for his eccentric behavior?",
    "options": [
      "Mayor Quimby",
      "Mayor McCheese",
      "Mayor Adam West",
      "Mayor Bee"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Mayor Adam West"
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "question": "What is the name of Stewie's evil half-brother, who is the primary antagonist in some episodes?",
    "options": [
      "Bertram",
      "Kevin",
      "Jake",
      "Stewbert"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Bertram"
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "question": "Which character in Family Guy is a police officer and uses a wheelchair due to a paralyzing accident?",
    "options": [
      "Cleveland",
      "Quagmire",
      "Joe",
      "Herbert"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Joe"
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "question": "Who is the Griffin family member known for his love of playing the tuba and is often seen with a hat covering his eyes?",
    "options": [
      "Chris",
      "Meg",
      "Stewie",
      "Brian"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Chris"
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "question": "In Family Guy, which character owns a store called 'Goldman's Pharmacy'?",
    "options": [
      "Mort",
      "Dr. Hartman",
      "Herbert",
      "Cleveland"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Mort"
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "question": "What is the name of the talking and anthropomorphic baby in the Griffin family?",
    "options": [
      "Stewie",
      "Brian",
      "Chris",
      "Meg"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Stewie"
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "question": "Which character is Peter Griffin's best friend and is known for his womanizing ways?",
    "options": [
      "Cleveland",
      "Quagmire",
      "Joe",
      "Herbert"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Quagmire"
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "question": "Identify the Griffin family member who is an accomplished pianist and often plays classical music.",
    "options": [
      "Peter",
      "Lois",
      "Chris",
      "Meg"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Lois"
  }
]
